<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pages on BTH Portfolio</title>
    <link>https://BigBrainWorld.github.io/philippecormierportfolio/pages/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pages on BTH Portfolio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://BigBrainWorld.github.io/philippecormierportfolio/pages/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Sound</title>
      <link>https://BigBrainWorld.github.io/philippecormierportfolio/pages/lab3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BigBrainWorld.github.io/philippecormierportfolio/pages/lab3/</guid>
      <description>MP3 Your browser does not support the audio element. An MP3 file is a type of digital audio file that uses a compressed audio format to reduce the file size while preserving most of the original sound quality. The MP3 format is a popular choice for distributing music and other audio content over the internet, as it allows for efficient storage and faster download times.
MP3 files use a lossy compression technique, which means that some of the original audio data is discarded during the compression process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://BigBrainWorld.github.io/philippecormierportfolio/pages/lab1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BigBrainWorld.github.io/philippecormierportfolio/pages/lab1/</guid>
      <description>Web Usability Web usability refers to how easy it is for users to navigate and interact with a website. It encompasses a range of factors, including the site&amp;rsquo;s layout, design, functionality, and content. A usable website is one that is easy to use, intuitive, and efficient, and provides a positive user experience. Good web usability can help to increase user engagement, reduce bounce rates, and ultimately drive business success.
Text Good web design involves using legible fonts, appropriate font sizes, and appropriate line spacing to make text easy to read.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://BigBrainWorld.github.io/philippecormierportfolio/pages/lab2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BigBrainWorld.github.io/philippecormierportfolio/pages/lab2/</guid>
      <description>Images In multimedia work, images are used to convey visual information, enhance the overall aesthetics of the work, and capture the attention of the viewer. They can be photographs, illustrations, diagrams, charts, or any other form of visual representation. Images can also be used to evoke emotions, set a mood, or create a specific atmosphere.
When incorporating images into multimedia work, it is important to consider factors such as image quality, size, and file format to ensure that the images look clear and crisp, load quickly, and are compatible with different devices and platforms.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
